## JASPER JOSHUA GEOLAGON

BS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

#### **PROFILE**

Hello I am Jasper Joshua Geolagon. For 9 years, I was a student leader, and for 4 years, I was a member of the school publication. My areas of expertise include article editing, broadcasting, and taking good pictures for memories. My experiences have shaped me as who I am today, broadened my horizons, and helped me develop my leadership and communication skills.



#### CONTACT

- **O** 0938-078-1186
- geolagonjasperjoshua@gmail.com
- Purok 1 Bitaugan, Antequera, Bohol

#### **SKILLS**

#### Writing

Broadcasting

Proofreading

Time Management

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### ibex

(October 2021 - February 2022)

Customer Service Representative

Worked at ibex a BPO company for 4 months as a CSR of Amazon handling Payment Methods of amazon users and Support in their mode of payment as well as retail queries providing refunds back to their original payment method and return of orders.

#### **SOFTWARE**

Canva

**MS Office** 

**HTML** 

CSS

#### **Work Imersion**

(2018 - 2019)

TVL (NC II Holder)

Work Immersion at Bayacabac Maribojoc as an organic agriculture student studying organic farming, and agricultural system that uses ecologically based pest controls and biological fertilizers derived mainly from animal and plant wastes and nitrogen-fixing cover crops.

#### **LANGUAGE**

**English Language** 

Filipino Language

Cebuano Language

#### **EDUCATION**

BOHOL ISLAND STATE UNIVERSITY - Balilihan Campus **BS Information Technology** 

(2019 - Present)

#### **EXTRA CURRICULAR**

# Student Supreme Government Senator President

2021 - present

- Designed and Managed virtual programs at school.
- Organized weekly meetings.
- Suggesting activities up for the proposal.

# Campus Journalism Associate Editor in Chief

2019 - 2020

• Reading and Editing articles to be published in the campus magazine.

## School Performing in the Arts

**President** 

2014 - 2019

- Undergo conferences and seminars for the improvement of the club.
- Dance Training every Friday.

#### REFERENCE

## BENJAMIN N. OMAMALIN, PhD,CpE. College of Technology and Allied Sciences - Dean

Bohol Island State University - Balilihan Campus Magsija, Balilihan, Bohol

# Hon. LEONARDA M. DABALOS Brgy. Captain

Bitaugan, Antequera, Bohol

I hereby certify that the above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

# **Student Supreme Government** P.I.O

2016 - 2017

- Clean the areas after school events.
- Design the stage for an upcoming school program.
- Making memos up for the proposal.

JASPER JOSHUA M. GEOLAGON

Applicant

## **Student Supreme Government**

Representative

2014 - 2015

- Attend meetings every Friday.
- Checking every room for the monthly category.
- Making certificates for the award every month.